<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Centos on CheshyTech Blog</title>
    <link>https://cheshytech.github.io/en/tags/centos/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Centos on CheshyTech Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.147.9</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://cheshytech.github.io/en/tags/centos/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CentOS Frozen Package Update</title>
      <link>https://cheshytech.github.io/en/posts/centos-7-frozen-package-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cheshytech.github.io/en/posts/centos-7-frozen-package-update/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After installing a CentOS 7 system and updating the repositories, you usually need to update packages. However, for some reason, one of these times, a package decided to become corrupted. Specifically, the package &lt;code&gt;initial-setup-0.3.9.30-1.el7.centos.x86_64&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When corrupted, during the process of cleaning up old versions after updating packages, it fails to delete itself, causing the update process to &amp;ldquo;freeze.&amp;rdquo; At this point, you might not know whether it is still working or has stopped.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outdated CentOS Repositories</title>
      <link>https://cheshytech.github.io/en/posts/outdated-repositories-centos-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cheshytech.github.io/en/posts/outdated-repositories-centos-7/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Some CentOS distributions can be a headache to install and configure, especially considering there are deprecated versions that no longer have support. CentOS 7 is one of them. I have created a series of articles, of which I would consider this the first, related to issues that may arise in such installations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The CentOS 7 repositories are no longer available at their original locations (the URLs have changed). This causes errors when trying to update system packages or install new ones, such as the following:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
